so I lock them to info or John thanks
for joining us Thank You Roger thanks
for having me so outlined for our
listeners who is the bustle of their
everyday responsibilities may not be
fully aware of what vol 7 has exposed
bulk 7 really is a very dramatic
revelation a very dramatic exposure of
what the CIA has been up to between 2013
and 2016 that Barack Obama's second term
remember the most transparent president
in American history well apparently the
most transparent president American
history had ordered the CIA to develop
acts into the iphone into the google
android phone into the samsung smart TV
and even into our car's computer systems
now if you're an intelligence service
and you're going after a hostile power
that's all great if you're going after a
terrorist group or you're trying to
target the Iranians or the North Koreans
that's great but what we don't know and
what many of us suspect is that the CIA
was using this technology or these
technologies to target American citizens
and for all we know they may have even
used this technology to target then
candidate Donald Trump it appears that
way it really should not be any surprise
that your handheld device that your
television set that so many of these
electronic devices that we have in our
homes and offices can be converted by
the government to be listening devices
on the advice of an intelligence
professional almost two years ago when
I'm having a particularly confidential
conversation would say Alex Jones or
somewhere else I will turn the phone off
and actually place it in another room
now some of my colleagues have told me
that that's crazy that's paranoia no I
think its technological reality tell you
that's not good enough
that's not good enough when I was at the
CIA and I'm talking about 10 15 even 20
years ago when I was at the CIA it
wasn't good enough to shut the phone off
or put it into another room because the
CIA can remotely activate the phone so
that it looks like it's off but it's
still functioning as a microphone so
what we would do until the days when you
could no longer take the battery out of
the phone if you couldn't take the
battery out you would put it in a
freezer and close the freezer or
refrigerator for that matter or leave
the phone in your car because the CIA
from anywhere in the world whether it's
Langley Virginia or somewhere overseas
they can activate that phone and
activate the phone's camera and can
record your whole conversation without
you even realizing that the device is on
it seems to me that we've had a
never-ending trail of the Central
Intelligence Agency getting caught with
misdeeds and lies being dragged before
the Congress and swearing they're really
sorry they'll never do it again then
they go back to Langley and of course
nothing ever ever changes I think the
president would be wise to clean house
if the CIA as soon as possible I was
rather surprised that in the inaugural
week he went out to Langley and kiss
their derriere I would not have done so
they are the enemy they are the tip of
the spear or the globalist and frankly
as they brought John Kennedy down as
they undermine Richard Nixon they have
every intention of undermining and DOD
legitimizing this present and keep in
mind Roger that this is still very much
Barack Obama CIA these people who rose
to the senior-most levels of the CIA
over the past eight years did so under
President Barack Obama they served under
John Brennan they served under David
Petraeus they served under
his name escapes me now the obama's
first CIA director Leon Panetta Iannetta
so these guys that while their career
intelligence officers they came of age
under Barack Obama now Jimmy Carter who
was one of the most wildly unpopular
president inside the CIA was unpopular
for a reason and it was because he
cleaned house he got rid of a lot of the
people who had been caught by the church
committee committing assassinations and
spying on Americans and doing all the
things that the law of the land says the
CIA should not be doing what he ended up
doing was firing literally hundreds of
senior operations officers in something
called the Friday night massacre people
that the CIA still talk about the Friday
night massacre the truth of the matter
is every once in a while you need to
carry out a massacre at the CIA because
the organization becomes to politicize
it becomes too polarizing and it ends up
working against the interests of the
president and the country and you have
to clean out well you as you'll recall
after Jimmy Carter appointed stansfield
turner the Admiral as the head of the
CIA most of those who work and in the
india in the massacre could later be
found over at the george bush for
president headquarters in Virginia and
of course almost all of them would make
their way back into the agency after
President Ronald Reagan made the mistake
of letting George Bush control the
intelligence agencies essentially gave
him the intelligence portfolio for the
Reagan years the abuses that the CIA are
legion no one ever seems to go to jail
no one ever really gets fired as you
know president john f kennedy threatened
to to what was it smash the agency and
then we have ian different pieces which
i believe played a major role in his
ultimate murder i think it is a factor
based on the bay of pigs in the cuban
missile crisis in which the the CIA
undermine kennedy and if you read my
book the man who killed kennedy the case
against LBJ i think i make a compelling
case that did that James Douglas in his
book John F Kennedy and the unspeakable
that the CIA is indeed complicit right
there so the real question I'm going to
ask you the same thing I asked George
niemeyer from American Spectator because
as a CIA veteran you have I think a good
perspective on these things where does
this go from here do you think a
congressional inquiry will will will
help us get at the truth or well let's
become a political circus and should we
have a judicial proceeding in which I
think now that Jim apartment now the
jeff Sessions the Attorney General has
recused himself I think prematurely he
still would have the authority to
appoint a special prosecutor somebody of
impeccable integrity with a pristine
reputation impanel a grand jury and
begin bringing the Obama security
apparatus bosses in front of the grand
jury one by one to find out what really
happened to you and that is exactly my
position I I don't trust Congress with
this at all and I think it's because
Congress has proven really since the
middle 1980s to be a little more than
cheerleaders for the CIA Dianne
Feinstein for example when she was the
chairman of the Senate Select Committee
on Intelligence did nothing to stop a
CIA malfeasance Anna all the years that
she headed that committee the same thing
has happened under Republican leadership
it seems that forever reach for whatever
reason members of the Senate Select
Committee on Intelligence and the house
permanent Select Committee on
Intelligence see their job as that of
just supporting CIA operations we don't
need any outside bodies to be supporting
CIA operations right now we
need an organization that can find the
truth that can get to the fact and
determine what if any crimes were
committed and I think the only way to do
that is with a special prosecutor and
panelling a grand jury I agree with you
on that one hundred percent well it
would certainly put so many in the
intelligence network in a position where
they could no longer dissemble for fear
of a perjury charge and it is if you
look back through history it is only
perjury charges and charges of contempt
of Congress that has spoiled CIA
officers in the past if you go all the
way back to the 70s if those two charges
that have wrapped people up you're
absolutely right I'm thinking of the
Defense Intelligence director on James
clapper under Barack Obama as you know
he already got caught lying to Congress
about how much metadata was being kept
on American citizens 26 senators
co-signed a letter accusing him of
perjury one senator demanded his
resignation the house leadership of the
Intelligence Committee was in open
revolt over his lies why should we now
suddenly believe mr. clapper when he
tries to make this all go away with an
incredible double whammy of well we
weren't surveilling the President and
there is no evidence that the Trump
campaign was in touch with the Russians
this is an attempt to close the barn
door after the horses have already
escaped he is only make this mess that
the actions of Langley are going to come
crashing down around his head and
there's nothing now I think that they
can do about it this is adorable as
nixon's men being caught and being tied
back to the Watergate break-in it is
only a matter of time I say all the time
that
the CIA told us that they were not
torturing prisoners there was no torture
program that was a lie the CIA said that
there was no secret prison system being
run outside the US judiciary that was a
lie the CIA said that they were not
sending prisoners to third countries to
undergo torture that was a lie the CIA
said that it was the Russians that
hacked the US election and practically
installed Donald Trump absolutely zero
evidence that any of that was true but
now they want us to just take their word
for it but they're not spying on
Americans and that they weren't spying
on Donald Trump what my view is every
time a CIA leader opens his mouth he's
lying so why in the world would we
believe him now yeah put another way how
can you tell they're lying at the CIA
their lips are moving no I think that
you are at you're exactly right and the
president however needs to clean house
you have an analogous situation at the
FBI why he has allowed mr. Comey who
covered up for the Clintons in the sandy
Berger affair covered up for the
Clintons in the Lamarck rich affair
covered up for the questions in their
initial illegal server controversy we're
incredibly the slices and dices all of
the things Hillary did in violation the
law and then announces that she won't be
prosecuted a time that in itself tells
you that by Election Day when he first
on Thursday said he was reopening the
investigation based on 650,000
additional new emails and then on Sunday
night i believe it was said well folks
we went through all 750 or 650 there's
nothing there mr. Comey has worn out his
credibility he has no more public
credibility it is time for Donald Trump
to make judge Jeanine Pirro we press the
head of the FBI she was a distinguished
prosecutor with a reputation for
integrity
and I guarantee you she's one tough lady
someone I've known for peace I guess 30
years going back to her days at the
westchester county district attorney she
could clean up the agency of that i have
no doubt and i also have no doubt that
the American people would rally around
the president if she initiated a change
like that not just an FBI but also at
CIA you know these these constant
accusations and amy windows are
exhausting not just for those of us here
in Washington but for Americans all
across the country the president can put
that to rest and can really put his foot
down by getting rid of these malcontents
and starting fresh